

# ARTUR JĘDRZEJCZAK FRONTEND DEVELOPER

# CONTACT

artur.jedrzejczak@gmail.com



+48 664 289 281



Poznan, Poland



github.com/aratur

# **SKILLS**

Frontend: React, React Router, React Query,

Redux, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, SASS, Jest, NodeJS,

Electron

Databases: Oracle DB, MS SQL Server,

MySQL, SQLite

Tools: Git, GitHub, Bitbucket, Jira,

DevTools, Postman, JMeter

IDE: Visual Studio Code, Atom, IntelliJ

# **EDUCATION**

Poznań University of Economics Master's Degree, Information Systems [ 2004 - 2009 ]

## CERTIFICATION

- · Oracle DB SQL Certified Expert
- Oracle Certified Associate, Java SE 8 Programmer
- IBM Data Science Professional

Certificate

· Professional Scrum Master (PSM I)

# **PROFILE SUMMARY**

Developer with almost 15 years of experience working with different technologies (over 2 years frontend) looking for a role as a mid/senior developer. Motivated, with willingness to learn new technologies and skills. Good team worker. Open to a B2B or an employment contract, remote work. Due to personal reasons a 4 day working week is preferred. Currently on a B2B contract, with a 30 days notice period.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## 07/2020 - PRESENT SENIOR DEVELOPER AT CAPCO POLAND SP. Z 0.0.

**Project:** Back-office application for HSBC

Responsibilities: Development of a fronted, banking applications for back-office employees.

Technologies: React, Redux, JavaScript, TypeScript, SASS, CSS, HTML

# **EXPERIENCE**

## 07/2020 - PRESENT PERSONAL FRONTED DEVELOPMENT MASTERY PATH

**Project:** Non-commercial projects done in a private time

Responsibilities: To practice my skills, I implemented some projects that are available on my

github account. They have live versions (links on github) so feel free to look through the code or see how it works. (work that I normally do is not publicly available). First two are from the time when I started working with React. Recent ones are based on web designs from <code>frontendmentor.io</code>, using ready designs allowed me to focus more on the implementation side of things.

Technologies: React, Redux, React Query, JavaScript, TypeScript, CSS, SASS, HTML

## 06/2017 - 07/2020 SENIOR DEVELOPER AT CAPCO POLAND SP. Z O.O.

Project: New internet banking for BNP Paribas Polska

Responsibilities: Building migration engines for Identity Management System and Payments

Implementation of micro-services in the area of system administration,

payments

**Technologies:** Oracle SQL, Java, Spring Boot, Hibernate, JMeter

# 11/2015 - 02/2017 CONSULTANT AT ACCENTURE SP. Z 0.0.

**Project:** Building a new Digital Bank in France for La Banque Postale based on mBank. **Responsibilities** Designing an architecture of payments and cards for the new bank using a fit-

gap approach.

Technologies: APIs, UML, software architecture

# **ONLINE VERSION OF THIS CV**



https://aj-cv.vercel.app/

## 01/2015 - 07/2015

## CONSULTANT AT ACCENTURE SP. Z O.O.

**Project:** Post-merger integration for mBank and BRE Bank

Responsibilities Implementation of Migration engine, Implementation of synchronization tool

between SharePoint and MS Project to track live-progress and reporting.

Technologies: C#, MS SQL Server, MS Project, SharePoint

## 03/2013 - 12/2014

## CONSULTANT AT ACCENTURE SP. Z O.O.

Project: Post-merger integration for Santander Bank Polska and Kredyt Bank

Responsibilities Implementation of Migration engine in Loans area including reconciliation.

Technologies: Ab Initio (ETL), MySQL

## 12/2010 - 11/2013

## ANALYST AT ACCENTURE SP. Z O.O.

**Project:** Flexcube Core Banking system implementation for DNB Nord

**Responsibilities** Operational reports delivery in loans area. Development of post-migration

reconciliation reports for corporate loans. Implementation of interface between

the Lithuanian Central Bank.

Technologies: SQL Server, Oracle DBL

## 08/2008 - 11/2010

## **DEVELOPMENT SPECIALIST AT BZ WBK S.A.**

**Project:** Transfer Agent implementation for Arka Investment Funds

Responsibilities Implementation of reconciliation reporting, and business reporting

Technologies: Oracle, Business Objects

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 10 maja 2018 roku o ochronie danych osobowych (Dz. Ustaw z 2018, poz. 1000) oraz zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych w zakresie przyszłych procesów rekrutacyjnych.